class SpeakingData {
  static List<QuestionAnswer> workStudyList = [
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: 'Do you work or are you a student?',
        answer: """I’ve been working as an English teacher for about 15 
Years now, and for the last 10 years I’ve specialized
 exclusively in teaching IELTS. And I absolutely love
 what I do. Of course, sometimes I feel tired and
 emotionally drained, especially when I have to mark my 
Students’ essays until midnight … but I just don’t see
Myself being happier doing anything else. 
"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: 'Do you work or are you a student?',
        answer: '''It’s been a few years now since I started working full 
time. I work in Experiential Marketing and I absolutely
 love it because it’s the type of job that really lets you
Utilize all of your talents. One day you can be making a
budget , and the next day you can be learning to use a
drill because you need to drill holes in the floor. It’s very
versatile. It’s for people who don’t want to be the same
as the day before . (by Elena Korobskaya, a band 9 
scorer, watch a video on our Instagram)
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: 'Do you work or are you a student?',
        answer: '''Well, when I left school, I got a degree in nursing 
I’ve been working as a nurse at X hospital for almost
Years now. Being a nurse is really hard .I’m responsible
For lots of different things such as preparing patient 
For examination, observing and recording patient
Conditions. Measuring and recording their vital signs
And weight. providing emotional support to patients  and
their families , administering medications ,preparing 
rooms, cleaning  and disinfection equipment and
instrument, or assisting doctors during surgery . This 
list is endless. Also every day I perform a really wide
range of tasks. To provide care to my patients and
resolve their problems . For instance, I thread and 
remove catheters , apply and change wraps and
bandages, feed patients who cannot feed themselves,
dress patients with physical challenges help 
ambulatory patients walk, turn bedridden patients to
 prevent pressure sores, and transport patients. There’s
No such thing as a routine day in a hospital, and you
Never know what to except. That’s why it’s very tough 
Job. 
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: 'Do you work or are you a student?',
        answer: '''I’m a student, and this is my final year at school. Now
I’m working hard in order to get passing grades to enter
College in Canada. If everything is ok, six, months ago
now I’ll already be studying there. I want to major 
Journalism  as I like writing essays and articles and want
to work for some famous magazine of newspaper .I’m
going to do a three- year course at X college .
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: 'Do you work or are you a student?',
        answer: '''I neither work nor study . At the moment I have a 
Bachelor’s degree and I’m planning to apply for a 
Master’s degree as soon as I meet the requirements of
the program. It seems I’ve missed the boat for the fall
semester, so I’ll try not to miss the deadline for applying 
for the winter one .
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: 'Do you work or are you a student?',
        answer: '''Neither. Having worked for many Years in the field of 
Advertising, I made a decision to upskill and now that I
have completed a program, I want to pursue a career in
IT.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: 'Do you work or are you a student?',
        answer: '''Currently I’m unemployed. Half a Year ago the company
I had been working at for many Years started massive
layoffs. One day I was made redundant among others
Unfortunately, I’m still looking for a job which would 
in line with my qualifications and experience, but
an easy task. 
'''),

    // next quuestions
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Why did you choose that job?''',
        answer: '''Well, I guess the primary reason why I decided to 
Pursue a career in Finance was that I really loved Math’s 
at school as I was always good at numbers . And
because of this , I thought it was the only possible
choice I could make. So it wasn’t a tough decision. And,
thank God, I have never regretted it. 
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Why did you choose to study that subjects?''',
        answer: '''Back in the day when I was a high school student, I had
an idea that I might like to do something related to
fashion , nut my parents insisted on my choosing
Accounting . Frankly, I wish I hadn’t listened to them as I
don’t really enjoy being an accountant

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Why did you choose that job?''',
        answer: '''Well, I guess the primary reason why I decided to 
Pursue a career in Finance was that I really loved Math’s 
at school as I was always good at numbers . And
because of this , I thought it was the only possible
choice I could make. So it wasn’t a tough decision. And,
thank God, I have never regretted it. 
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Why did you choose to study that subjects?''',
        answer: '''Back in the day when I was a high school student, I had
an idea that I might like to do something related to
fashion , nut my parents insisted on my choosing
Accounting . Frankly, I wish I hadn’t listened to them as I
don’t really enjoy being an accountant
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Do you like your job?''',
        answer: '''I do. Mainly because it’s never boring. I love challenging 
tasks. In fact, the more challenging, the better. Of
Course, I usually spend a lot of time and energy, put a 
Lot of effort in order to complete such tasks
Successfully, but job satisfaction that it gives me
Significantly outweighs the hours, the stress and the 
hard work. Among   other things, there’s nothing to
adequate, let alone all the perks that my employer
Provides.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question:
            '''New!! (for nurses) Is there anything you dislike about Your Job?
''',
        answer: '''I’d rather say there are things that are really hard to 
manage or cope with. The hardest thing is that as a
nurse know what to expect. Also, you have to work long
hours, work on weekends, holidays and during night
Workloads and paperwork.  What’s more, you spend
most of the time walking ,standing , lifting and bending ,
something, trying to test the limits of your patience. But
despite all this, I don’t think I could do anything but 
nursing now.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''What do you dislike about your job?''',
        answer: '''Well, I hate that I often have to work against the clock
to meet deadlines and it seems that I’ll never be able to
escape this constant rat race.  I feel this jam packet
schedule is robbing me of my life.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''What do you dislike about your job?
''', answer: '''The only thing that I don’t like is too much
responsibility. Of course, when I chose this job, I Knew
What I was getting into, but sometimes I can’t help
feeling envious and be responsible for the rescue 
the whole company .
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Do you like your job?''',
        answer: '''I do. Mainly because it’s never boring. I love challenging 
tasks. In fact, the more challenging, the better. Of
Course, I usually spend a lot of time and energy, put a 
Lot of effort in order to complete such tasks
Successfully, but job satisfaction that it gives me
Significantly outweighs the hours, the stress and the 
hard work. Among   other things, there’s nothing to
adequate, let alone all the perks that my employer
Provides.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question:
            '''New!! (for nurses) Is there anything you dislike about Your Job?
''',
        answer: '''I’d rather say there are things that are really hard to 
manage or cope with. The hardest thing is that as a
nurse know what to expect. Also, you have to work long
hours, work on weekends, holidays and during night
Workloads and paperwork.  What’s more, you spend
most of the time walking ,standing , lifting and bending ,
something, trying to test the limits of your patience. But
despite all this, I don’t think I could do anything but 
nursing now.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''What do you dislike about your job?
''', answer: '''Well, I hate that I often have to work against the clock
to meet deadlines and it seems that I’ll never be able to
escape this constant rat race.  I feel this jam packet
schedule is robbing me of my life.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''What do you dislike about your job?
''', answer: '''The only thing that I don’t like is too much
responsibility. Of course, when I chose this job, I Knew
What I was getting into, but sometimes I can’t help
feeling envious and be responsible for the rescue 
the whole company . 
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''What was your dream job when you were Young?
''', answer: '''Oh, when I was younger, I wanted to either become a
CEO of a big company or be self-employed. I was really
 Sure that this would bring me an adequate remuneration
and, as a result , a sense of satisfaction. What is more, I
Managing, people, could  take on responsibility and work
under pressure, which was very important for pursing
such careers.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Have you changed your mind on your dream job?
''', answer: '''Well, on the whole, ‘no’ as this is what I still dream
about. However, now I realize that there are quite a lot
Or things in this career which I didn’t think about at a 
younger age, for example, the fact that working under 
pressure is robbing people of their life, talking them
from their families and pushing them to participate in 
the rat race in order to get recognition and good 
Money.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''What do you like about your studies?
''', answer: '''I will probably sound a bit nerdy, but I’m happy that 
School provide me with an opportunity to acquire
Knowledge about things I didn’t know before. I guess
that most subjects. We are taught. Will help us to
succeed in the future. So I never miss lessons and
complete all the assignments on time.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''What do you like about your studies?
''', answer: '''As a high school student, I can safely say that I dislike 
School very strongly mainly because the teachers pile
So much work onto us  that we hardly get 5 hours of 
Sleep a night during an average school week. You see,
no matter when I go to bed, I have to wake up early
Because my classes usually start 8 am. To top it off,
Most subjects are boring and irrelevant to our future
Careers. So it causes a lot of stress, making me and my
fellow students reluctant to study.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''What do you dislike about your studies?
''', answer: '''Well, my pet hate is that the school curriculum doesn’t
take into account individual differences and capabilities
of students. All of us are different, but we are supposed
to study the same subjects at the same pace. Also, I
Don’t like the fact that our educational system relies
Heavily on teamwork. Of course, I realise they’re trying 
to teach us to collaborate, but I think it’s unfair that
everyone gets the same grade irrespective of how
much each person has done. '''),
  ];

// --------------------------------------------------------------------

  static List<QuestionAnswer> homeTownList = [
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Please describe your hometown a little. 
''', answer: """ Well, Delhi is the capital of India and by far the largest 
     city in the country. It's a densely populated place, so 
             the city is always crowded and noisy. Also, Delhi has 
             the highest number of vehicles, therefore traffic 
            congestion is a norm here. Also, it has very rich history.
            For this reason, it’s really popular with tourists who
            Come to visit our wonderful temples and experience 
           Indian culture. It's never boring to live here as the city
          provides a wide array of entertainment options. It is also 
         home to our government and all major institutions.
"""),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Tell me a little about the place where you live 
''', answer: '''I live in Hong Kong. And I should say it's a truly unique 
place. When people generate an image in their heads of 
what Hong Kong looks like, they envision a concrete 
jungle. They imagine movies with famous skyscrapers 
dominating the skyline. Yeah, this is true that the
 lots of skyscrapers here. But actually, it's the biggest
 misconception about Hong Kong cause almost 65 per
 cent of its territory is parks, beaches, and mountain
 And there are lots of amazing hiking trails. Another
 interesting fact is that Hong Kong is one of the ways 
 most expensive places to live in Despite  this it's one of
﻿most heavily populated cities in the world. Nearly 
7,5 people live here. So, there is a lot of busy city life
 going on here, day and night. And it's one of the world's
 most densely populated areas too, especially Hong 
Kong island. It has a population of more than 1 million 
people although it's relatively small. It takes just one 
hour to travel from one side of it to the other. Since the 
population in is very dense, it is very common for 
apartment buildings to have forty floors and for
 apartments to be very small. That's probably the only 
thing that makes me upset, but I'm used to it. As I've
 said before Hong Kong Island is quite small, so 
everything is linked quite closely, and the underground 
system is really efficient. It can take you anywhere 
want to get to. I love living here.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Please describe your hometown a little.
''', answer: ''' My hometown has just about one hundred thousand 
 people which are regarded as a small one. But describe 
 small size, people have a full access to the same
facilities as a large city offers such as department
 stores, schools, cafes, hospitals ... you name it. So, l 
never feel trapped or limited in opportunities. There 
aren't many vehicles here, so it isn't noisy and polluted.
 What is really important is that there are no traffic jams 
even during rush hours.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''What is your town well-known for? 
''', answer: '''Well, as it's a resort town, people from all over the 
country as well as from abroad come there to have a 
rest, sunbathe, swim, breathe sea air and eat delicious
 seafood. At the height of the season, usually in July, the
 city is packed with people. My hometown is famous for
 its rich nightlife as well. Along the harbour there are 
some amazing nightclubs and bars for spending an 
unforgettable night out.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''What is your town well-known for? 
''', answer: '''I believe a wealth of history and culture is a primary.
 source of attraction for tourists. People come there
 visit museums and many places of historic value U
 as X and Y. Every street is steeped in history. As the
 city is very old,  it consists of several parts. And walking
 around it, you can experience a journey through 
civilizations.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''What is your town well-known for? 
''', answer: '''You see, as it's an industrial city, I'm afraid, there's 
nothing it can boast of. There are neither ancient 
buildings nor other places of interest that could
 possibly attract tourists. However, it is in my city that 
the best shoes are produced.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Do you like your hometown? 
''', answer: '''Yeah, it is never boring no matter what your interests. 
It's a large city, so you can easily find where to go and 
what to do. One thing I particularly like about it is that although it is vast, there are a thousand small and intimate places there such as 
peaceful gardens a small friendly restaurant.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Do you like your hometown?
''', answer: ''' I'm afraid not. I don't think it's a great place for living 
 and what irritates me most is the quality of our road  
driving a car every day turns into continuous detecting 
﻿potholes instead of focusing on the road traffic. It's
 more than frustrating. Unfortunately, this list goes on 
and on. There are too few green zones so the city looks 
like the forest of high-rise office and residential 
buildings. You know, it's impossible to get a lung
' Fresh air unless you drive 30 kilometers away from 
city. And yet, the cost of living is incredibly high.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Is that a big city or a small place?
''', answer: ''' It's neither small nor big. Actually, it largely depends on
 what city you compare it with. I would say it's big,
 enough to provide city dwellers with all necessary 
facilities, whereas it's nowhere near as large as New
 York or Sydney, for example.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Is that a big city or a small place? 
''', answer: '''Well, I'm from one of those everyone-knows-everyone 
towns. So, I have no trouble meeting people face to face
 and I'm glad all the facilities are within walking distance.
 Just imagine, it takes just X minutes to get from one
 end of my hometown to the other.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Is that a big city or a small place?
''', answer: ''' I live in a huge sprawling city. No, to say 'huge' is to say 
nothing causes if you view the city from a tall building.
 you get the feeling that it doesn't end. It's so big that it 
takes hours to go from one side of the city to the other.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''How long have you been living there?
''', answer: ''' Well, I've been living there since I was born. At times |
 leave the city just for a while when I go on holidays.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''How long have you been living there?
''', answer: ''' I'm new to the area and even don't know anyone and
 Anything. So I can't help feeling lonely, but I hope things 
Will improve in the near future.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''How long have you been living there?
''', answer: ''' I've been living here for 2 years now. I had to move here 
to be with my husband who was offered a job here. And 
I understood that turning down that offer was out of
 question.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Do you think you will continue living there for a
 Long time? 
''',
        answer: '''Every time an opportunity to move to a different place
 Turns up, I come to realise that I want to be here above
 Everywhere else as the city is rich in everything you
 Could possibly desire. There are lots of things to do and
 Places to go. What is most important for me is that X is
 The city of infinite possibilities for ambitious and career
Driven people like me as a lot of large international
 Companies have chosen it for their headquarters.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Do you think you will continue living there for a
long time?
''',
        answer: ''' Well, I want to move to a larger city as soon as possible
 As living here is unlikely to give me a chance to
 Implement my goals and make my all dreams come 
True. I've tried to, but couldn't find a decent opportunity.
 Locally. So, given half a chance, I'll try to start a new life
 In a different place.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''
Do you think you will continue living there for a
            Long time? 
''', answer: '''   No way will I stay here forever! To be honest, I've 
     Planning to move to a new place for a long time a
     Really fed up with hustle and bustle of a large city. And 
   Living here is nothing but the rat race. You know, I feel
   I'm already on the verge of getting burnt out.
'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Would you like to live in the countryside in the future?
''',
        answer: '''Oh no! Not until I retire! I'm only 25 and dreaming of a 
    High-flying career, but I'm afraid that living in the 
  Countryside will leave my career in tatters. Besides, I'm 
 A very active and sociable person, so I think I will be 
 Bored to death being deprived of an active social life
 And abundance of entertainment options a big city
   Provides.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Well, this isn't what I'm dreaming of. I'd rather say I
''',
        answer:
            ''' don't mind swapping city life for a rural idyll. I'm tired of
 the constant rat race and I'll definitely enjoy a slower 
pace of life. Also, I want to live in a house with multiple
 rooms, a garage and swimming pool which is obvious
 not possible until I move out of the city.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''What is the difference between living in the countryside
 And the city? 
''',
        answer: '''I guess that the most striking difference is that if you are 
 Countryside there isn't much traffic even during rush
 Hours. Again, as there are fewer vehicles emitting
, exhaust fumes, rural areas are nowhere near as
 Polluted as urban ones. So the air is definitely fresher
. This is why it's highly likely that people living in the
 Country live longer. However, there may be a number of
 People who won't appreciate these benefits as they
 Aren’t many opportunities for professional growth? 
 The choice of facilities is limited.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''There's generally not much to do in the countryside,
''',
        answer: '''   Especially in the winter, so I'm sure the majority of 
              Young people like to chat with their friend online or play
             Computer games. They may also like to get together in
             Order to play football, ride bicycles or explore the
            Surroundings. This is because if children are not glued 
        To their devices, they usually have active pastime. The
       More adventurous, the better. Again, as the number of 
      Recreational facilities is severely limited in the
      Countryside, it seems to me that the most popular
     Activity with adults is having barbeque parties or just
       Chatting with their neighbors over the fence.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''How has your town changed over the last 20 years?
''',
        answer: ''' Oh, I would say it has undergone sweeping changes 
'cause those who haven't been there for a long time
 can hardly recognize it. First of all, the general quality 
of the city landscape has improved, so it's way more
 Beautiful now. For instance, many ancient buildings
 Have been restored and modern ones have been
 Erected. Therefore, it has turned into a remarkable
 Tourist attraction.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''How has your town changed over the last 20 years?
''',
        answer: ''' Well, as far as I can see, the city has undergone
 Tremendous changes as it has turned from a small
 Peaceful town into a large bustling city. It's now 
Approximately twice as large as it used to be. So it 
Means that now it can boast improved infrastructure, 
More places to visit and things to do as a lot of facilities
 have been made available for people. Overall, I'd
 Say the city has changed for the better, though there are
 Still issues with public transport which is as inefficient 
As many years ago.

'''),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''How has your town changed over the last 20 years
''', answer: ''' In my opinion, there has hardly been any notice
 Changes over the last two decades. It's just a lot more
 Crowded now. There's more traffic, and therefore more 
Pollution. Of course, several modern buildings have
 Been erected and the infrastructure somewhat
 Improved but I would say these changes are for the
Worse as the town has lost its identity it used to
Better place to live in 

'''),
  ];

  // --------------------------------------------------------------------

  static List<QuestionAnswer> countryList = [
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Tell me a little about your country ?''',
        answer: """Well, Russia is the largest country in the world,
 Occupying about one-sixth of the world's surface. It's
 Largely an industrial country and one of the most
 developed world's economies. As it's so large, it
 encompasses whopping 9 time zones and has a variety.  """),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Tell me a little about your country? ''',
        answer: """Oh, there are so many things I can tell you about it... I
 Don’t even know where to start. Well, first of all, Ukraine 
Is a large country situated in the heart of Europe.
 There's even some place that Ukraine claims
 To be Europe's geographical center. It's not far from Rakhiv, a
 Small town in the Carpathian Mountains. In fact, it's just
 A board with an inscription. Another interesting fact I
 Found out about recently is that with 70% of Ukrainian
 Adults having a secondary or higher education Ukraine 
Ranks fourth among the most educated nations, and it
 Has the fourth highest number of certified IT
Professionals in the world. However, I don't know how
Reliable this information is. Also, one quarter of the
 World’s black soil reserves are located in Ukraine. And
 Because of its properties our black soil is consider
Best in the world. Well, what else... the country is
 Washed by the waters of the Black Sea and the St
 Azov in the south. And there's a mountain range in the
 West. To tell the truth, I can spend hours speaking
 About my country.
 """),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Which part of your country do most people live in?''',
        answer: """As far as I know, almost 10% of the country's entire 
Population lives just in one city, in Moscow. It is an
 Interesting fact, taking into account that Russia is the 
Largest country in the world. The second most
 Populated city is St. Petersburg. Both Moscow and
 St. Petersburg are attractive to people because there
 Are more jobs on offer than in other cities in Russia.
  """),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Where is your country located? ''',
        answer: """Well, I'm not very good at geography, but from what I 
Remember India is located in Southeast Asia, sharing the
 Border with 6 or 7 countries in the north. Its land 
Neighbors include China, Nepal and Bangladesh
That's for sure. Also, India borders the Arabian Sea, the
 Bay of Bengal and the Indian Ocean in the south.   """),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Tell me about the main industries in your country? ''',
        answer: """ As far as I can judge the most lucrative sector is
 Manufacturing.. It seems that the goods that aren't
 Produced in China simply don't exist. And I don't even
 Doubt that it manufactures more goods than the rest of
 The world combined. China is one of the world's biggest
 Producers of toys, textiles, apparel, electronic... you
 Name it. Also, the country's economy relies heavily on
 Agriculture. The dominant agricultural product is
, undoubtedly, rice. Besides, China grows wheat
, tobacco, potatoes, peanuts, soybeans, corn, tea and
 Oilseeds.
   """),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Tell me about the main industries in your country? ''',
        answer: """Well, as far as I know there are 3 industries driving, 
Ukraine's economy. Firstly, Ukraine is a leading global
 Agro-export player. For example, it's the breadbasket of
 Europe. It's also one of the world's top wheat exporters
 And the world's third largest producer of barley.
 Secondly, another lucrative sector is machine building.
 For instance, Ukraine has been and still is a world
 Leader in rocket building. Also, I know for sure that
 Transportation vehicles manufactured by Ukrainian
 Economy include cars, trucks, buses, railway car
 Diesel locomotives, airplanes, and ships. Finally
Ukraine is a major producer of steel and iron as the
 Country has abundant reserves of iron and other ores.
   """),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''What are some of the good things and some of the bad
 Things about living in your country?
 ''',
        answer: """I think the greatest problem is poverty. Many people
 Have so low incomes that they can hardly make ends
 Meet. Some of them cannot afford even basic needs
 like food and housing. This makes people resort to
 Committing crimes in a desperate attempt to survive.
 However, the good bit is that there are signs that the
 Economy is recovering and the government is taking,
 Measures to fight poverty. So, things will probably
 Improve soon.
   """),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''What are some of the good things and some of the bad
 Things about living in your country?
 ''',
        answer: """I would say the greatest benefit is that people here
 Enjoy a high quality of living. What I mean is, in general,
 The incomes are high, the level of unemployment is
 Comparatively low. Everyone has an opportunity to
 Obtain education and find a well-paid job. However, all
 This means higher taxes, but what you get is noticeable.   """),
  ];

  // -------------------------------------------

  static List<QuestionAnswer> part2Test1 = [
    QuestionAnswer(
        question:
            '''Describe an experience when you were not allowed to use a mobile phone.
''',
        answer: """The most recent occasion when I couldn't use my
 Smartphone was last month when I was on board a
 Plane flying to X.

             At first, all the passengers boarded the plane and took
           Their seats. When the plane was ready for takeoff, the
             Pilot came over the intercom, greeted the passengers
          And asked everyone to either switch off the phones or           
            Use them in an 'airplane mode', which shuts off phone
            Transmissions during the flight.

           I quickly turned off mine and was really surprised that
          There were still people who refused to follow the rule
           And had a confrontation with a flight attendant.

I know (as I read some articles dedicated to this that
 This may not be so critical an issue when the is 
Already at cruising altitudes as there's no direct 
Evidence of mobile phones or other devices interference
 With aircraft systems, but it's really important due to
 Takeoff and landing phases because of its possible.
 Interference with ground networks, which is dangerous
. You know, there's also no proof that wireless devices
 Do not cause any problems, and I'm sure that the signal
 Of the phone does interfere with navigation instruments
 And can cause instrument display malfunctions. So
 Even during the flight I kept my phone and other
 Devices turned off 'cause I didn't want to be
 Responsible or share responsibility for a crash.

"""),
  ];

  static List<QuestionAnswer> part2Test2 = [
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Describe a time when you did shopping in a street market.
''',
        answer: """Several years ago my best friend and I were on holiday
 In X country. Our tour guide recommended us to go to
 The city's oldest street market, which is one of the
 Oldest shopping streets in X, always abuzz with local
 People and holidaymakers who go there to buy spices,
 Fruit, clothing, souvenirs, handicrafts, fabrics, to name
 But a few. He told us that this would be a great way to
 Get an interesting glimpse into local culture and do
 Shopping, and it indeed was an unforgettable life
 Experience.

Now I can safely say that it's by far the most crowded
 Street I have ever seen. Both sides of a narrow medieval
  Street were teeming with people, it was just like a bee
 Hive. Vendors all vied in offering their goods to
 Shoppers. Shoppers from all over the world were
Swarming around stalls so I had to squeeze through
 Crowd to get a closer look at anything that was such
 Couldn’t even stop and look around as the crowd
 Literally dragged me along. It was really noisy.
Despite all the difficulties, I managed to buy spices
 My mom as she likes cooking and some local
Handicrafts and souvenirs because I collect such
 Things.

With my friend, whom I was travelling with, 
 But no sooner had we reached the place than we were
 Separated by the crowd. So we quickly understood that
 There was no point in trying to resist in order to keep
 Together. I just tried to look around every other minute
Not to lose sight of her. For this reason, I can say I went
 There on my own.

 Oh, and I nearly forgot one thing. I had to be very
 Careful not to become pickpockets' victim because
Such crowded places are a paradise for them. 
Interesting as the market's vibrant atmosphere my 
. Shopping lots of fun. But it was a bit dangerous too. 


"""),
  ];

  static List<QuestionAnswer> part2Test3 = [
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Describe a puzzle that you solved.
''', answer: """Well, when I was a child, I was a jigsaw puzzle
             Enthusiast. I assembled puzzles whenever I had a spare
            Moment. But after I had completed a 5000-piece
            Gradient puzzle, I lost interest in this activity. Since then 
            I've been given lots of them, but they are still
            Unopened, collecting dust on some shelf.

 The only puzzle that I have completed since childhood 
Was a 3D wooden mechanical pendulum clock puzzle
 That my friend gave me for my birthday last year. I was
 Really excited 'cause it was something new for me. And I
 Was hoping it would be challenging as well.

 I thought it would take me a while to assemble it,
 But it took me a minute to figure out the process. And once
 You have the hang of it, it's super easy and lots of fun
 So I put it together, all by myself in just a few hour
 There were easy to follow instructions. And need
 Neither glue nor scissors to put it together. The only
 Challenge I faced was that some pieces required a 
 Deal of hand strength to snap together. But it was 
 'cause they snapped together perfectly, making it
Almost impossible to break apart once its assembled.

 So even though it wasn't extremely challenging
, I enjoyed solving it 'cause doing jigsaw puzzles is a really
 Good way to unwind after a hard working day and 
spend quality time on your own.


"""),
  ];

  static List<QuestionAnswer> part3Test1 = [
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Is it a waste of time to take pictures with
 Mobile phones?

''', answer: """Well, I'd say both yes and no. It can be regarded as a
 Waste of time if people want to create professional
Looking photos that they can be proud of as,
 Unfortunately, smartphone photos usually have low 
Picture quality, compared to those made by professional
 Cameras. But it isn't a waste of time if people need
 Photos for sharing with friends on their social networks
 And in all kinds of messengers. Above that,
 Smartphones make it easy for people to take
 Photographs and capture memories irrespective of
 Where people are and without special training thanks to 
Phones' auto-focusing, auto-metering and easy-to-use cameras.
 To sum up, I wouldn't say that taking 
Smartphone pictures is a waste of time, except those
 Cases when people need professional-looking photos.

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Is it a waste of time to take pictures with
 Mobile phones?
''', answer: """ Well, I'd say both yes and no. It can be regarded as a
 Waste of time if people want to create professional
Looking photos that they can be proud of as,
 Unfortunately, smartphone photos usually have low 
Picture quality, compared to those made by professional
 Cameras. But it isn't a waste of time if people need
 Photos for sharing with friends on their social networks
 And in all kinds of messengers. Above that,
 Smartphones make it easy for people to take
 Photographs and capture memories irrespective of
 Where people are and without special training thanks to 
Phones' auto-focusing, auto-metering and easy-to-use cameras.
 To sum up, I wouldn't say that taking 
Smartphone pictures is a waste of time, except those
 Cases when people need professional-looking photos.

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''What positive and negative effects do mobile phones
 Have on friendship?

''',
        answer: """ On the one hand, and it's obvious, smartphones make it
 Easier to keep in touch with friends, and therefore they
 Help you keep connected with your friends no matter
 How far apart you are. You can text your friends, make
 Video calls any time you want. You can disclose any
 Personal information and respond to others in their
 Social networks. However, smartphones, originally
 Designed as a communication tool, actually hinder
 Rather than foster interpersonal connectedness.
 Unfortunately, there are many situations in which you
 Ignore friends in favor of a mobile phone. For example,
 You feel the quick buzz of our phone and feel
 compelled to see what's happening, even if that means
 Turning your attention away from other people. When
 you are on your phone, you are not looking at other
 People and not reading their facial expressions, tears in
 Their eyes, frowns, smiles. You don't hear the nuances
 in their tone of voice, or notice their body posture. For
 Example, I used to have a friend who checked her
 Phone so much when we were together that I finally
 Told her she had to choose — me or her phone. Also
 There are many situations in which you are middle
 Scrolling through the latest news or playing a game.
 Instead of chatting with your friends. But giving your
 Time, energy, thought, and attention to your
 Smartphone instead of the person you're with is
 Gradually ruining your friendships 'cause your friends
May feel ignored and pushed away. I'll tell you more,
 Just having a phone out and present during a
 Conversation (say, on the table between you) interferes 
With the sense of connection to the other person
 The quality of the conversation. This phenomenon it
 Especially the case during meaningful conversations.

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Do young and old people use phones in the same way?
''',
        answer: """Oh, definitely no. Seniors generally lag behind their
 Younger counterparts especially when it comes to using
 Mobile phones. The only pattern they share is voice
 Calling. In other patterns old people are usually second
 To the young. Teens and young adults are more
 Enthusiastic users of cellphones, they are also bigger
 Users of text messaging. I guess the young send and
 Receive at least five times more messages a day than
 Older people. Younger adults tend to use their phones
 For multimedia content, for taking pictures or video, for
 Accessing Internet. They are also more likely to turn to
 Their phones to avoid others around them or to fight
 Boredom. All this is still strange for the old.

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: ''' What are the differences between writing a letter and
    Writing a text message on a cell phone?

''',
        answer: """ Oh, there are quite a few of differences, actually.
 First of all, writing a text message is faster than writing a
 Letter 'cause text messages are generally much shorter.
 Secondly, messages are instant while letters can take
 Weeks to be delivered, which makes communication? 
More complicated. On the other hand, it is more
 Personal to write by hand as it adds a human touch to
 The relationship. Handwritten letters always convey
. Greater effort and greater care taken and let recipients 
Know that they are important for somebody.


"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Many people think mobile phones can be annoying at
 Times. Can you give any examples of that? 
''',
        answer: """Well, one of the examples when I get annoyed with a 
Mobile phone is when the phone ring interrupts an
 Important conversation or distracts my attention from
 What I really need to do at the moment. Another
 Annoying case is when people talk loudly on their
 Phones on public transport. Such phone conversations
 Grab my attention and don't let me relax or focus on my
 Thoughts, which I dislike. I can also get irritated when 
People around play music loudly on a phone 'cause it
 Shows their disrespect to others, which I don't consider
 Appropriate. These are the main situations I don't like to
 Get in.
"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Many people think mobile phones can be annoying at
 Times. Can you give any examples of that? 

''',
        answer: """Well, one of the examples when I get annoyed with a 
Mobile phone is when the phone ring interrupts an
 Important conversation or distracts my attention from
 What I really need to do at the moment. Another
 Annoying case is when people talk loudly on their
 Phones on public transport. Such phone conversations
 Grab my attention and don't let me relax or focus on my
 Thoughts, which I dislike. I can also get irritated when 
People around play music loudly on a phone 'cause it
 Shows their disrespect to others, which I don't consider
 Appropriate. These are the main situations I don't like to
 Get in.

"""),
  ];

  static List<QuestionAnswer> part3Test2 = [
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''What is the difference between street markets and 
Super markets?

''',
        answer: """Well, supermarkets are self-service stores while
Markets are places where sellers serve buyers. One
More difference is that supermarkets are indoor shops
While street markets are located outdoors. I’d also add
That the conditions inside supermarkets are more
Comfortable than those of the street markets, I mean
Those shops are always warm in winter and cool in
Summer. And the most important difference, to my 
Mind, is that produce at street markets is more fresh,
And sometimes more diverse, than that in
Supermarkets.

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Do many people go the street markets in your country?
''',
        answer: """Well, quite a few, actually. People like Visiting Street
Markets as there is always a variety of products to
Everyone likes and budget. What is more, the
Produce there is always fresh and usually lasts longer
Than that from the supermarket 

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Do you like going to street markets?
''', answer: """I do, but not very often. I don’t like crowed and noisy 
Places very much, but at the same time I adore to buy
Fresh high –quality products, Oh, and I also adore to
Bargain at the markets, so I’d rather say I like visiting
Them than out 

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''What are the advantages and disadvantages of
Shopping at a big shopping Centre?

''', answer: """Oh, one of the biggest advantages of shopping at a
Large shopping mall is a chance to visit a variety of
Shops without having to spend a lot time on going to
Different areas of the city. Another advantage is a
Chance to get both shopping and entertainment
Opportunities at a single location... Oh, and, of course,
And opportunities to park a car thanks to vast parking  
Areas… As far as disadvantages are connected, I’d 
Lay emphasis on huge crowds of people, especially at
Weekends and on holidays, and the temptation to buy
unnecessary things because of sales and special
Offers…

What are the advantages and disadvantages of
Shopping at a big shopping Centre?
Oh, one of the biggest advantages of shopping at a
Large shopping mall is a chance to visit a variety of
Shops without having to spend a lot time on going to
Different areas of the city. Another advantage is a
Chance to get both shopping and entertainment
Opportunities at a single location... Oh, and, of course,
And opportunities to park a car thanks to vast parking  
Areas… As far as disadvantages are connected, I’d 
Lay emphasis on huge crowds of people, especially at
Weekends and on holidays, and the temptation to buy
unnecessary things because of sales and special
Offers…

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Why is online shopping popular these days?

''', answer: """ I believe there are many reasons, really. First of all, it's
 Convenient. You don't have to make time, drive all the 
Way to a store and, god forbid, if the items you were in
 The pursuit of appeared to be unavailable. On the
 Internet, you can buy whatever you want in a matter of
 Seconds without interrupting other activities. You can
 do it literally on the go. All you need is to have a
 Payment card and any Internet-enabled device. Further,
 Online shops can offer prices which are hard to beat as
 Costs of their operations are substantially lower than
 those of traditional ones. Also, it is without doubt
 There’s a much larger selection than any traditional 
Store can possibly keep in stock. Many people like
 Online shopping as it gives them access to products
 They can't buy locally. I guess in general online 
shopping has become so popular with people because
 It’s absolutely hassle-free.

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Do you think online shopping will replace shopping? 
In reality? 

''',
        answer: """Well, chances that in-store shopping will entirely disappear
 Are slim. The thing is no matter how popular
 Online shopping will be, there will always be some items 
Those shoppers simply won't countenance buying
 For example, I don't doubt that more and more 
 Will buy things that are mass produced online as thin,
﻿Are exactly the same no matter where you purchase
 Them. So you don't need to personally inspect these
 Items to know if they are what you are really looking for.
 However, many people are likely to continue doing. 
Shopping in a traditional way when it comes to 
Shopping for clothes as, in most cases, it is necessary
 To try them on before buying. Otherwise, people 
Wasting a lot of time sending stuff back.

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Why is online shopping popular these days?

''', answer: """ I believe there are many reasons, really. First of all, it's
 Convenient. You don't have to make time, drive all the 
Way to a store and, god forbid, if the items you were in
 The pursuit of appeared to be unavailable. On the
 Internet, you can buy whatever you want in a matter of
 Seconds without interrupting other activities. You can
 do it literally on the go. All you need is to have a
 Payment card and any Internet-enabled device. Further,
 Online shops can offer prices which are hard to beat as
 Costs of their operations are substantially lower than
 those of traditional ones. Also, it is without doubt
 There’s a much larger selection than any traditional 
Store can possibly keep in stock. Many people like
 Online shopping as it gives them access to products
 They can't buy locally. I guess in general online 
Shopping has become so popular with people because
 It’s absolutely hassle-free.


"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Do you think online shopping will replace shopping? 
In reality? 

''',
        answer: """Well, chances that in-store shopping will entirely disappear
 Are slim. The thing is no matter how popular
 Online shopping will be, there will always be some items 
Those shoppers simply won't countenance buying
 For example, I don't doubt that more and more 
 Will buy things that are mass produced online as thin,
﻿Are exactly the same no matter where you purchase
 Them. So you don't need to personally inspect these
 Items to know if they are what you are really looking for.
 However, many people are likely to continue doing. 
Shopping in a traditional way when it comes to 
Shopping for clothes as, in most cases, it is necessary
 To try them on before buying. Otherwise, people 
Wasting a lot of time sending stuff back.

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Do you think men and women have the same?
 Shopping habits?

''', answer: """ Definitely no! Women usually treat shopping as a fun
 Experience or an adventure while men perceive it as an
 Errand or chore. What is more, women mainly shop 
Based on future needs (food for next week, a cocktail 
Dress for an upcoming party.). While men tend to
 Purchase when the need is immediate. Women usually 
Compare prices; spend a lot of time hunting down
 Bargains and prefer to do shopping together with their
 Friends while men seldom compare prices, don't care if 
The item is on sale and generally shop alone. So, there 
Are a lot of differences between female and male 
Shopping habits, to my mind.

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''How often do people in your country go shopping?

''', answer: """Well, it entirely depends on what products they are
Looking for. The majority of people, I think go to a
Supermarket almost every day to buy fresh bread and 
Some everyday items which they’ve run out of. I mean
Some household goods, personal hygiene products and
Water. Many people have a habit of going to a local 
Farmers’ market at weekends to buy some fresh fruits
And veggies because produce is usually offered within
24 hours post-harvest. As for such things as household
Appliances or clothes, they are brought more seldom as,
Firstly, they are rather expensive and, secondly, people
Don’t need new ones so often. 

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''What kinds of places are popular for shopping in
 Your country?

''', answer: """ I guess a number of people nowadays are doing
 Shopping online as a price is really hard to beat due to
 The fact that costs of operations of online shops are
 Substantially lower than those of traditional ones. Plus,
 It’s really convenient. People can do shopping when
 And where they want. However, there are still many 
People who would not trade shopping experience at
 Large department stores for the world. For many of
 Them, it's a way to have fun and relieve the stress
 Addition, many customers still want to touch, fee
l check the quality goods before making purchases.

"""),
  ];

  static List<QuestionAnswer> part3Test3 = [
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Why do people like digital mind games?

''', answer: """ Well, I think, first of all, this is because digital games are
 Easily accessible, I mean that they are either low-cost
 or free and can be downloaded in a matter of seconds. 
Also, they are a great way to fight boredom while
 Commuting, waiting in lines, or during other
 Uninteresting routines. Also, these games can be played
 On the go and they don't take up much of people's time.
 Well, and the last reason I'd like to mention is that going
Digital can help the environment as digital copies do not
 Have all those paper covers, paper instruction booklets
 or cardboard cartons that are very slow to decompose.
 These are the main reasons, to my mind.
"""),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Why do people like digital mind games?

''', answer: """ Well, I think, first of all, this is because digital games are
 Easily accessible, I mean that they are either low-cost
 or free and can be downloaded in a matter of seconds. 
Also, they are a great way to fight boredom while
 Commuting, waiting in lines, or during other
 Uninteresting routines. Also, these games can be played
 On the go and they don't take up much of people's time.
 Well, and the last reason I'd like to mention is that going
Digital can help the environment as digital copies do not
 Have all those paper covers, paper instruction booklets
 or cardboard cartons that are very slow to decompose.
 These are the main reasons, to my mind.
"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Are mind games like crossword puzzle games popular
 in your country?

''',
        answer: """Oh yeah, they are as they provide people with an
 Opportunity to unplug and give themselves and family.
 An escape from the information overload that is buzzing. 
Through the very fabric of our lives 24 by7. The reason
 why I'm saying 'themselves and family is because mind
 Games are both a great way to spend quality time alone
 And connect with family while working toward a shared
 Goal. Well, and one more reason why puzzle games are
 So popular in my country is because they are a kind of
 Mental workout that improves people's problem-solving.
 skills and attention span which are of primary
 Importance for those who want to succeed in our busy, 
Competitive world.

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Why do people like mind games?

''', answer: """ Well, I think that, first of all, people like mind games
 Because these games help them evaporate the
  Of everyday life giving them a kind of an escape
  The information overload that is buzzing through the
 Very fabric of modern life 24 by_7. So, first of all, people
 Use puzzles as a great meditation tool and stress
 Reliever in the contemporary world. The second reason
 Why people opt for mind games, as it strikes me, is
Because mind games are a great way to spend quality
 Time both alone and with close people. Well, and one
 More reason which explains people's interest in puzzles
 is the fact that mind games are a kind of mental 
Workout that improves people's problem-solving skills 
And attention span which are of primary important
 Those who want to succeed in our busy, competition
 World.


"""),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Why do parents let their children play puzzles?

''', answer: """ Well, I think parents do so because they understand
 That puzzles can be a valuable tool for children to learn
 New things as well as keep the mind active and working
. What is more, it is common knowledge that puzzles
 Present many benefits for children's development. For
 Example, kids develop hand-eye coordination, enhance
 The large movements of kids to the point where they
 Can then work on their fine motor skills, which lead to
 Better handwriting and typing skills. Also, puzzles give
 Children the chance to use adaptable thinking,
 Deduction and reasoning skills as kids figure out how to
 Put the puzzle together. Well, and one more benefit of
 Playing puzzles is the fact that they deepen children's
 Understanding of how to follow directions to achieve
 Their goals. I guess these are the main reasons why
 Parents let their kids do puzzles.

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''What kinds of puzzles improve people's intelligence?

''',
        answer: """ Well, unfortunately, I'm not well-versed in mind-teasers 
And know not that many kinds of puzzles but among
 Those kinds which I know, I would give prominence to
 logic puzzles, Sudoku puzzles and crosswords as they 
Exercise parts of the brain that may not be stimulated
 Otherwise and this way increase our neuroplasticity, or,
 In other words, improve our intelligence. Also, these
 Kinds of puzzles require thinking in unconventional 
Ways with given constraints in mind, which boosts our
 Brain activity in general and logical thinking in
 Particular. So yeah, I think that these are the puzzles
 Which improve our intelligence more than any other
Mind games.

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(question: '''Why are detective stories attractive to people?

''', answer: """

 Oh, I think detective stories appeal to so many people
, First of all, because people have a natural drive to pick
 Up the details, piece them together and find out who
 Committed the crime before the murderer is revealed by
The detective. This means that people like detective
e stories because such stories invoke their imagination
 And let them get gripped by the suspense of whodunit
. What is more, detective stories offer people a sense of
 Vicarious satisfaction as well as escape from the fears,
 Worries, strain and stress of everyday life. Well, these
 Are the main reasons why people get fascinated by this
 Type of stories, to my mind.

"""),
    QuestionAnswer(
        question: '''Which is better, a detective movie or its original novel? 
''',
        answer: """Well, for me an original novel is much better than a
 Detective movie. The first reason why it is so is because 
Novels give in-depth understanding of characters and
 Plot while movies are more a kind of summary of books.
 What is more, while reading a novel I always pay
 Attention to every line, imagine how things are going 
And create the scenes in my head in fine detail. When it 
Comes to movies I just see everything as it is without
 Giving my imagination a chance to fill my head with
 Amazing pictures which usually far exceed the visual
 Effects displayed in movies. And the last reason why I
 Love original novels more than films is because 
Watching a movie is quite quick while reading a novel is 
A lengthy process which makes me even more involved
 In the plot and extends my pleasure.

"""),
  ];
}

// ---------------------------------------------------------

class QuestionAnswer {
  final String question;
  final String answer;

  QuestionAnswer({
    required this.question,
    required this.answer,
  });
}
